Guide to the Samuel R. Pierce papers, 1961-1985.
Pierce, Samuel R. papers
- Series XII. Photographs
  - Photos of Awards, Plaques, and Memorabilia 2, No Date (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Black and white
  - Photos of Awards, Plaques, and Memorabilia 3, No Date (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Photos of Awards, Plaques, and Memorabilia 4, No Date (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ministerial Level Meeting, OECD, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Glen Cove School Visit, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Visit to Ottawa, No Date (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Ambassador Niles, Ambassador Britton
  - Secretary Pierce in China, No Date (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - US/USSR Fifth Joint Committee Meeting on Housing and Other Construction, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Signing of Protocol and Wreath laying ceremony at Arlington Cemetery, June 23-24
  - Secretary Pierce HUD Photos, No Date (Box 28, Folder 11)
    David Valdez
  - HUD at Adoption Partnership Ceremony, Jefferson High School, No Date (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - HUD Photos 1981, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    White House Press Briefing, National Association of Home Builders, National Association of Regional Councils, U.S. Conference of Mayors, Testimony, National League of Cities Executive Director, Glen Cove School, Trip to Alaska, National Press Club, House Republican Study Committee, Labors International Union Meeting, HUD Informational Forum for Women, Tuesday Club Forum, Republican National Committee, David Valdez
  - HUD Photos 1982, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    U.S. Conference of Mayors, Mid Winter Conference of National Governors Association, Pension Fund Press Briefing, Annual Federal Aid Seminar, Girls Nation Delegate, David Valdez
  - HUD Photos 1983, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Opportunities Industrialization Center Revitalization Ceremony, David Valdez
  - HUD Miscellaneous Photos, No Date (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Urbana Development and Diane Camper NEWSWEEK, Leonard Burchman (Assistant to Secretary Pierce), Interview on WOR/WNEW, Marion Barry, Opportunities Industrialization Center, Announcement of National Selections for Senior Citizen and Handicapped Housing in Chinatown NYC, Vice President Bush and President Ronald Reagan, Fair Housing Campaign, David Rockefeller, CPD, Northern California Black Chamber of Commerce, Visit to Pittsburgh, Advisory Council of Historic Preservation, Photos with Asian Politicians, David Valdez
  - Donald Ingvald Hovde, No Date (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Official White House Photographs, 1981-1988 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Ronald Reagan (hand-signed photographs), George H. W. Bush, President Traore of Mali, Minnie Wilkins, Republican National Committee, Fair Housing Amendments Signing Ceremony, Cabinet Meetings, Conferences, Malvin R. Goode, Long Island University
  - Samuel R. Pierce Various Photos 1, 1981-88 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Bankers Mortgage in Florence, HUD Departure, meetings, satellite, funeral, circus, 1988 Republican National convention, Secretary of State George Shultz, Barbara Bush, U.S. Conference of Mayors, Soviet Union, Japan, Singapore Stock Exchange, The Embassy of the People's Republic of China, Thomas A. Bolan, Ted Britton, Jet Magazine, UDAD Check - City of Akron, U.S. Savings Bonds, Home Builders Institute
  - Samuel R. Pierce Various Photos 2, 1981-88 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Richmond Renaissance Groundbreaking, George H. W. Bush, Martin Luther King Jr. Federal Holiday, Battery Park City Corporation Authority, John Heinz, Tom Bolan, Columbus OH, Signing of the Protocol - Moscow, House of Representatives, Donald Schaefer, Fair Housing, Lewis Glueck - Southern Brooklyn Community Organization, Jack Anderson, OECD, Home Builders Institute, Republican National Committee, Village of Hempstead
  - Samuel R. Pierce Various Photos 3, 1972-88 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Sentinel Society Inc., John Connally, Asian Bank Meeting 1972, William Rogers, Martin Luther King. Jr. National Holiday Celebration, Portraits, Inc., 25th Anniversary of President Nixon's Inauguration (Nixon hand-signed), George H. W. Bush
  - Rosa Park, Martin Luther King Jr. National Holiday Celebration, meetings, press conferences, local business visits, 1932 Olympic Site, CFC, Home Builders Institute, Interracial Council for Business Opportunity, Samuel R. Pierce Apartments, Air Force One, Ted Britton, Akron OH, National Organization of Disability, National Minority Procurement Fair, National Press Club, Ronald Reagan, Pope John Paul II, Pierce football photos, Miscellaneous (Non-Labeled) Photos (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Secretary Samuel R. Pierce, Jr. First Year U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development Album, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Fair Housing Act Album, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Photo: United States Attorney's Office, 1953 (Box 34)
  - Poster: Signed North American District Heating and Cooling Institute Poster, No Date (Box 34)
  - Photo: Pierce Taking Oath, No Date (Box 34)
  - Photo: 66th Annual Dinner of Agudath Israel showing 1988 Humanitarian Award - May 15, 1988, 1988 (Box 34)
  - Photo: Official Photograph of Samuel R. Pierce, Jr., No Date (Box 34)
    Two copies
  - Photo: Official White House Photograph of Pierce and Richard Nixon, 1970 (Box 34)
  - Photo: George P. Schultz congratulates Samuel Pierce on receiving Alexander Hamilton Award (Award is in box 41), 1973 (Box 34)
  - Photo: Visit to Florence, South Caroline, 1, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Photo: Visit to Florence, South Caroline, 2, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Photo: Reagan, Bush, and Cabinet Members, Hand-signed by All Members, No Date (Box 39)
  - Photo: Reagan, Bush, and Cabinet Members, Hand-signed by All Members (different from above), No Date (Box 39)
  - Photo: Board of Directors Meeting, Arkansas Governor Bill Clinton, Guest of Honor, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Photo: Reagan, Bush, and Cabinet Members, Hand-signed by All Members, No Date (Map-case DD-23)
- Series VIII. Certificates
  - Certificate: Jefferson County Kentucky - Honorary Captain of the Belle of Louisville, 1981 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law - Appreciation, 1978 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: City of Glen Cove's Congratulatory Certificate for Induction into the Long Island Sports Hall of Fame, 1988 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: University of the State of New York Education Department - Certificate for Barbara Penn Wright M.D. to Practice Medicine and Surgery, 1949 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: The Home Builders Association of Maryland - Honorary Member, 1985 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: University of the District of Columbia - Adjunct Professor, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: Borough of The Bronx - Samuel R. Pierce, Jr. Day, 1987 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: Phi Delta Phi - Honorary Member, 1982 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: Senate of the United States in Executive Session - Secretary of Housing and Urban Development, 1981 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: State of New York, City and County of New York - Assistant District Attorney, 1950 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: The United States Department of Labor - a Member of the National Defense Executive Reserve of the Department of Labor, 1963 (Box 34)
    Signed by The Secretary of Labor W. Willard Wirtz
  - Certificate: Institute of Judicial Administration - a Member of The Institute of Judicial Administration, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: National Press Club - Appreciation, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Certificate: La Ciudad de La Villita - Mayor, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Certificate: The Great Navy of the State of Nebraska - Admiral in the Great Navy of the State of Nebraska, 1985 (Box 36)
  - Certificate: The Great Navy of the State of Nebraska - Admiral in the Great Navy of the State of Nebraska, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Certificate:President of the United States of America - Appointment to a Member of the National Commission for the Review of Federal and State Laws Relating to Wiretapping and Electronic Surveillance, 1973 (Box 40)
    Signed by Secretary of State Henry A. Kissinger and President Richard Nixon
  - Certificates: The People of the State of New York - a Member of the Banking Board, 1964, 1967, 1969 (Box 40)
  - Certificate: Attorney General of the United States Herbert Brownell, Jr. - Appointment to Assistant United States Attorney for the Southern District of New York, 1953 (Box 40)
  - Certificate: Boy Scouts of America - Rank of Eagle Scout, 1936 (Box 43)
  - Certificate: State of Louisiana Executive Department - Colonel on the Staff of Governor David Green and Aide=de=Camp, Governor's Staff, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Certificate: Secretary of State of New Mexico Clare Jones - Appreciation, 1984 (Box 44)
  - Certificate: The Advisory Group to the Commissioner of Internal Revenue - Appreciation, 1975 (Box 44)
  - Certificate: President of the United States of America - appointment to a member of the Advisory Council for Minority Enterprise for a term of two years, 1969-09-17 (Box 48)
    Signed by President and Secretary of Commerce
    Nixon, Richard
    Stans, Maurice H.
  - Certificate: Member of the Battery Park City of Corporation Authority, 1968-07-26 (Box 48)
  - Certificate: Judge of the Court of General Sessions of the County of New York, 1960-01-01 (Box 48)
  - Certificate: United States Court of Claims - admitted and qualified as an Atterney and Councellor, 1963-12-13 (Box 48)
  - Certificate: Town of Hempstead - proclamation for black history month, 1982-02 (Box 48)
  - Certificate: Town of Hempstead - citation, 1982-02-28 (Box 48)
  - Certificate: Office of the Executive, Nassau County - citation, Undated (Box 48)
  - Certificate: Office of the Executive, Nassau County - citation, Undated (Box 48)
- Series IX. Degrees
  - Degree: Cornell University Bachelors of Arts Degree, 1947 (Box 34)
  - Degree: Voorhees College - Doctor of Laws Degree, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Degree: Voorhees College - Citation for the Doctor of Laws Degree, citation, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Degree: The Trustees of Cornell University - Bachelor of Laws, 1949 (Box 34)
  - Degree: Elizabeth City State University - Doctor of Humane Letters, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Degree: Saint Augustine's College - Doctor of Humane Letters, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Degree: Central State University - Doctor of Laws, 1986 (Box 39)
  - Degree: Syracuse University - Doctor of Laws, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Degree: University of Syracuse - Doctor of Laws, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Degree: Miles College - Doctor of Letters, 1987 (Box 40)
  - Degree: Morehouse College - Doctor of Laws, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Degree: Delaware State College - Doctor of Civil Laws, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Degree: Tougaloo College - Doctor of Laws, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Degree: Bethune-Cookman College - Doctor of Laws, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Degree: Tuskegeensis University - Honorary Doctor of Laws, 1986 (Box 44)
  - Degree: New York University - Honorary Degree of Doctor of Laws, 1972 (Box 44)
    Signed by New York University President James M. Heste
  - Degree: Long Island University - Doctor of Laws, 1986 (Map-case DD-23)
    Signed by President David J Steinberg and Chariman of the Board of Trustees William Zeckendorf, Jr
  - Degree: Bishop College - Doctor of Humane Letters, 1986 (Map-case DD-23)
  - Degree: Virginia State University - Doctor of Laws, 1982 (Map-case DD-23)
  - Degree: New Jersey Institute of Technology - Doctor of Humane Letters, 1981 (Map-case DD-23)
    Signed by President
  - Degree: Baruch College - Doctor of Laws, 1986 (Map-case DD-23)
- Series X. Orders
  - Order: Ronald Reagan - Appointment of Samuel R. Pierce, Jr., to Chairman of the Interagency Committee for the Purchase of United States Savings Bonds, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Order: Appointment to the General Counsel for the Department of Treasury, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Order: Santa Fe, New Mexico - Secretary Samuel R. Pierce, Jr. Day, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Order: Albuquerque, New Mexico - Secretary Samuel R. Pierce, Jr. Day, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Order: Appointment to the Secretary of Housing and Urban Development, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Order: Appointment to a Member of the President's Advisory Council on Private Sector Initiatives, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Order: Appointment to a Member of the Advisory Council in Historic Preservations, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Order: Ronald Reagan - Appointment of Samuel R. Pierce, Jr., as Member of the Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1981 (Map-case DD-23)
    Signed by Ronald Reagan and William Clark.
  - Order: Abraham D. Beam - Appointment to Mayor's Special Commission of Inquiry Into Energy Failures, 1983 (Map-case DD-23)
- Series XI. Awards and Gifts
  - The Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Republican Presidential Commemorative, Honor Roll, No Date (Box 4)
  - Republican Presidential Legion of Merit, Presidential Honor Roll, No Date (Box 4)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee, Presidential Order of Merit, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Certificate of Attorney and counselor, Solicitor, Advocate, and Proctor of District Court, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Certificate of Board of Directors of the New York World's Fair, 1964 (Box 4)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee, Presidential Commission, 1992 (Box 4)
  - J. Edward Lumbard, United States Attorney, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Herman R. Henry Scholarship Foundation, Man of the Year Award, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Republican Presidential Task Force Life Member, Wall of Honor, 1993 (Box 4)
  - The University of the State of New York Education Department, College Entrance Diploma, 1940 (Box 4)
  - The Presidential Trust, Delegate from the State of New York in the 1992 Presidential Trust, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Young America's Foundation, Conservative Leadership Award, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Republican National Committee, Chairman's Honor Roll, 1997 (Box 4)
  - The Federal Tax Forum Inc., Honored Speaker, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Signed Dollar Bill (by the Treasurer of the US and the Secretary of the Treasury), 1981 (Box 4)
  - Trustees of Hofstra University, Degree of Doctor of Laws, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Florida housing Cooperative, Inc., Certificate of Appreciation, 1986 (Box 4)
  - City of Louisville, Honorary Citizen of Louisville, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Photo of Earth from the Moon, No Date (Box 4)
  - National League of Cities, Certificate of Appreciation, 1983 (Box 4)
  - National Press Club, Certificate of Appreciation, 1987 (Box 4)
  - The United States Department of Labor, Appointment of Assistant to the Under Secretary, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Howard University, Meritorious Award, 1977 (Box 4)
  - International Paper Company, Expression of Appreciation, 1994 (Box 4)
  - The President of the United States of America, Appointment of Firth Lieutenant, Judge Advocate General's Corps, 1950 (Box 4)
  - The President of the United States of America, Presidential Citizens Medal, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board and System, Fifty Years of Service, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity Inc. - Dedicated Service and Outstanding Leadership, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Knoell Homes - Cooperation in the Development of Cimarron, 1984 (Box 22)
  - The Black Advisory Committee of the 50th Presidential Inaugural - Distinguished Service and Significant Contributions to the USA, 1985 (Box 22)
  - River Park Towers Tenants Association Inc. - Outstanding Leadership and Public Support of the Fair Housing Amendment Act of 1983, 1984 (Box 22)
  - The Friends of Yelverton, Inc. - Outstanding Support and Cooperation in Furthering Education for Minority Students, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Tireless Efforts in Providing Moderate-Low and Affordable Housing for the Tenants of Salem Manor, Omaha, Nebraska, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Independent Republican Club of Harlem - Many years of Dedicated and Devoted Public Service and Outstanding Contribution in the Fields of Housing and Economic Development, 1984 (Box 22)
  - The US Hispanic Chamber of Commerce - Recognizing the Needs and the Potential of the Hispanic Community and Its Business Sector, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Holy Trinity Baptist Church Enterprises, Inc. - Commitment to Fair Housing and Outstanding Leadership, 1984 (Box 22)
  - National Conference of Black Mayors, Inc. - Stalwart Leadership and Untiring Commitment to the Full Development of Communities and Cities Throughout the Nation, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Phada Annual Convention - Outstanding Contributions to Public and Indian Housing, 1988 (Box 23)
  - The Council of 100 Black Republicans - Distinguished Service Award, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Huntsville Coalition of Small and Minority Businesses - Superb Leadership in the Private and Governmental Sectors, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Frederick Douglas Republican - Leadership Achievement Award, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Glen Cove High School - Glen Cove Hall of Fame, 1984 (Box 23)
  - National Association of Real Estate Brokers - Q. V. Williamson Memorial Appreciation Award, 1987 (Box 23)
  - The National Association of Home Builders - Development of Better Communities and His Commitment to Promote Affordable Housing for All Americans, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Atlanta University and Morehouse College - Leadership and Achievements and Establishment of The Samuel R. Pierce, Jr., Chair in Real Estate Studies, 1986 (Box 23)
  - The National Association of Neighborhoods - Outstanding Public Service, 1987 (Box 23)
  - San Diego Kind Corporation - Outstanding Cooperation and Commitment to Affordable Housing for the Elderly in San Diego, CA, 1988 (Box 24)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Office of the Secretary - Designation as a member of the National Defense Executive Reserve of the Department of Labor, (date) (Box 24)
  - City of Oakland - Fair Housing Day Proclamation, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Phi Beta Kappa - Member Certificate, 1943 (Box 24)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Member Certificate, 1947 (Box 24)
  - The Cornell University Athletic Association - Cornell Major "C" for Football Season of 1941, 1941 (Box 24)
  - Cornell Student Law Association - Certificate of President, 1948 (Box 24)
  - State of New York Executive Chamber - Reappointment to the Court of General Sessions, 1959 (Box 24)
    Hand signed by Nelson A. Rockefeller
  - Bar Association of Nassau County, NY - Distinguished Service Medallion, No Date (Box 24)
  - The Club At the Commissioner General's Lounge - Appreciation for support of the United States National Pavilion, Tsukuba Expo 85, 1985 (Box 24)
  - City of Atlantic City - Proclamation of Secretary Samuel R. Pierce, Jr. Day, 1987 (Box 24)
  - City of Buffalo - Key to the City, No Date (Box 24)
  - Northeast Regional Black Republican Council - Continuous Devotion to Quality Housing for the People of Our Region, 1987 (Box 25)
  - Bronx Shepherds Restoration Corporation - Years of Unswerving Commitment and Dedication to Bronx County, 1987 (Box 25)
  - CHAPA - Commendation, 1986 (Box 25)
  - City of Riviera Beach, Florida - Key to the City, 1986 (Box 25)
  - National Black Republican Council of the Northeastern Region - Untiring and Dedicated Efforts Towards Improving the Quality of Life of the Citizens, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Lincoln Coalition - To Pursue and Implement the Thoughts of Freedom, Unity and Honesty to American Principles of Abraham Lincoln, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Dedicated Service to Improving the Quality of Life in the Various Communities Across the Continental United States, 1984 (Box 25)
  - City of Compton, California - Key to the City, No Date (Box 25)
  - The Criminal Investigation Division Agents Association, Inc. - Distinguished Service and Dedication, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Republican Black Caucus - Man of the Year Award, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Treasury Interagency Savings Bonds Committee - 1983-84 Chairman, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Ginny Mae - Mortgage-Backed Certificate Guarantee for Criterion Financial Corporation, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Ginny Mae - Mortgage-Backed Certificate Guarantee for Drexel Burnham Lambert Inc., 1985 (Box 26)
  - The Long Island Black History Month Committee - The Black History Month Award, 1982 (Box 26)
  - West-Bro Community Development Corporation - Years of Service, Dedication, and Effort, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Illinois Black Republican Council - Outstanding and Meritorious Achievement, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Parents Association of C.E.S.229 - Outstanding Services to the People of the City of NY, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity, Inc. Zeta Mu Chapter - Certificate of Merit (Man of the Year), 1985 (Box 26)
  - The City of Hayti Heights, Missouri - Key to the City, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Long Island Council Afro-American Republicans - Outstanding Contributions and Sincere Commitment, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Balanced Government for America - Outstanding Contributions and Support of The National Conference of Black Majors, Inc., 1987 (Box 26)
  - City College Newman Club Award, 1960 (Box 26)
  - City of Florence, South Carolina - Pens and Pen Holder, No Date (Box 26)
  - National War College - Pens and Pen Holder, No Date (Box 26)
  - Shiloh A.M.E. Zion Church of Staten Island, N.Y. - Dedication and Service, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Brown Highbridge Republican Club - Accomplishments and Contribution in the Field of Housing and Community Affairs, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Northern California Black Chamber of Commerce - William Byron Rumford Award, 1984 (Box 27)
  - YMCA - Outstanding Efforts for the Renovations and Additions of Our Facility and Support of Our Youth, 1988 (Box 27)
  - YMCA of Greater New York - For Service to Youth, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Careers Incorporated - Humanitarian Award, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Penna Black Republic Council - Excellence Award, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Independent Republican Club of Harlem - Recognition Award, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity, Inc. Delta Gamma Chapter - Outstanding Services to the U.S. Government, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Harvard Model Congress - Appreciation, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency - Appreciation, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Boy Scouts of America - Whitney M. Young Jr. Service Award, No Date (Box 27)
  - Bausch and Lomb Honorary Science Award, No Date (Box 30)
  - Governor's Club Certification, No Date (Box 30)
  - Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks of the World, Inc. Necklace, No Date (Box 30)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development Pin, No Date (Box 30)
  - Republican Presidential Legion of Merit Medal and Pin, No Date (Box 30)
  - WWII Efficiency, Honor, Fidelity, Good Conduct Medal, No Date (Box 30)
  - North Shore Championships Nassau County, 1960,1944 (Box 30)
  - Boy Scout Merit Badges, No Date (Box 30)
  - Lewis Glaser Handcut Colonial Style Goose Quill Pens, No Date (Box 30)
  - Signatures: HUD, "To Secretary Pierce, with deep appreciation", No Date (Box 34)
  - Award: Cornell Law School Distinguished Alumnus Award, 1988 (Box 34)
  - Award: Southern Brooklyn Community Organization - Humanitarian Award, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Award: National Black Republican Council - Appreciation, Book of Laws Clock, November 1987 (Box 38)
  - Letter: From Ronald Reagan Regarding the Signing of H.R. 1158, the Fair Housing Amendment Act of 1988 (Reagan-signed Parker Pen included), 1988 (Box 35)
  - Award: The United States Hispanic Chamber of Commerce - Commitment and Contributions, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Award: B'nai B'rith Youth Services - The Real Estate and Construction Industry Man of the Year Award, 1985 (Box 36)
  - Cartoon: Vanity Fair Cartoon, Dec 11, 1869 - Judges No. 1 "The Lord Chief Justice of England", No Date (Box 36)
  - Award: Key to the City of Florence, South Carolina, No Date (Box 37)
  - Award: Richardson and Lucas, Inc. - Outstanding Dedication and Unswerving Support for the Building of Quality Housing, 1987 (Box 37)
  - Award: Community School Board 9, Bronx, N.Y. - Untiring Commitment, Support and Unswerving Dedication to the Improvement of Housing, 1987 (Box 37)
  - Award: The New York State Council of Black Republicans - Outstanding Contributions Towards Enhancing the Quality of Life in the Field of Housing, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Award: The Resident Advisory Committee of William Mead Homes - Operation Build Youth, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Award: Forth Worth, Texas - Honorary Citizen, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Award: The City of New Orleans - Honorary Citizen, 1981 (Box 39)